That hydrogen my name is Jyoti Agarwal
and Joshi's then I had appointed a teacher
and unlocked an update is very big for
him ICU special that Bharti AXA's
life insurance business is going to
melt with IAS body
and whatever is the Sharon juice of Bharti AXA
from 115 in return for this, the fault advice of 19 March
travel only and your non-life
insurance, so that will match because
you know Lamba's general insurance
company, IAS business was already
very big, it will make it even bigger, if
seen, Bharti and Akter
Group together have a holding company, here
both have folded together, so Bharti
Enterprises, as far as I know, has one per
cent stake holder, which other
friends, we do this point percentage here, so
with a very big jio4gvoice, we will see
what impact it has on IAS romantic
in the future but when we muscles glutes
light now an insurance company stitching
9084 understand B coming events have happened